Denis Arce

Full Stack Web Developer

Full stack web developer with Business Management and Banking experience educated at University of Texas at San Antonio. Skills in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript and strengths in managing teams, learning new technology, creativity, and teamwork. Successfully implemented new processes which increased organizational and efficiency in work processes.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance, San Antonio, TX — Full Stack Web Developer

JUNE 2021 - PRESENT

Web Developer with Management and Finance experience, developing and implementing applications and solutions using a range of technologies and programming languages.

Bank of America, San Antonio, TX — CSR 2

JULY 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2021

Provided the best solutions for clients based on their financial needs and introduced the various high-tech and high-touch choices they have to do their banking in ways that are most convenient for them.

BECU, Spokane, WA — Financial Member Consultant

APRIL 2018 - MAY 2019

Properly Identified and problem solved issues relating to member's accounts, transactions, applications, and procedures, while following federal regulations related to loan products.

EDUCATION

UTSA, Texas — Full Stack Web Developer

June 2021 - January 2022

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development.

Heritage University Washington — Business Administration

May 2010 - May 2014

Bachelor of Arts in Business Administration and Marketing.

San Antonio, Texas LinkedIn: /DenisArce GitHub: /D-Y-A-G Portfolio: Denis Arce (509) 759-8521

dnsarce21@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

JavaScript ES6+

CSS3

HTML5

SQL

NoSQL

JQuery

TOOLS

Express

React

Node

Handlebars

Query

Bootstrap

Foundation

Bulma

APLICATIONS

GitHub

MongoDB

MySQL

PROJECTS

Food-Truck-Fix – A custom app builder for Food-Truck owners!

Checkout App! #Repo

K9Cupid — A social app for humans best friends!

Checkout App!

#Repo

Concert Tracker — A social app for humans best friends!

Checkout App!

#Repo

Budget Tracker — A social app for humans best friends!

Checkout App!

#Repo